about the incident response for the collection tools. So, the steps are really, really
a simple one. So, you can simply block the hash of the vendor, but there is a problem.
So, if you block the hash of the vendor or so many users in the organization, they will
be also using the vendor. So, if you block the hash, the other users will also get
impacted the application will be get removed. So, instead of that, you can create
application control policy. So, that policy will apply for all the users. They will not
use the vendor temporarily inside the organization. So, we will not do it. If you observe
the rare file, there was not a product to the mega. And, but the threat tactic created
a rare file, you can delete the rare file from the machine. So, that is the another thing
you can that another incident response thing you can do. But initially, you observe a vendor
or someone there was involving in collecting the data, you can do these response actions
like creating an application control policies to block the applications by using the using
in the organization. So, we do not do any other things for that.
Let us hope from here and we will continue our discussion in the next section. See you guys.